=The Shoufu Can Read Mind=
= الشوفو يستطيع قراءة العقل =
=Episode 5=
= الحلقة 5 =
(If I'm able to find her a husband,)
(إذا تمكنت من العثور عليها زوجًا ،)
(he'll surely return the favour by giving me a lot of money.)
(سيرد الجميل بالتأكيد بإعطائي الكثير من المال).
What are you thinking about,
بم تفكر،
Shen Zhihuan?
شين تشيهوان؟
Although
بالرغم من
you're not beautiful,
انت لست جميلة
you
أنت
are my brother's
هي لأخي
wife.
زوجة.
You're at least
أنت على الأقل
more blissful than
هناء أكثر من
the ladies in Great Sui.
السيدات في Great Sui.
Yes!
نعم!
Your brother
أخوك
is outstanding.
رائع.
Marrying him
الزواج منه
is
يكون
the greatest thing I could've ever done in my life.
أعظم شيء يمكن أن أفعله في حياتي.
But...
لكن...
But what?
ولكن ماذا؟
Dan Zhu,
دان تشو ،
go out.
الخروج.
Do you know
هل تعرف
why your brother never slept with me
لماذا لم ينام اخوك معي قط
even though we've been married for half a year?
رغم أننا تزوجنا منذ نصف عام؟
Come on.
تعال.
My brother
أخي
is not interested
غير مهتم
in you
فيك
and
و
your body.
جسمك.
Mengchun,
Mengchun ،
well,
حسنًا،
I can't
لا أستطبع
bring myself to tell you this.
أحضر نفسي لأخبرك بهذا.
Looking ugly
تبدو قبيحة
is not your fault.
ليس خطؤك.
There's nothing shameful to talk about it.
لا يوجد شيء مخجل للحديث عنه.
Look at them.
انظر اليهم.
It's your brother.
إنه أخوك.
It's him.
إنه هو.
His kidneys are not good.
كليته ليست جيدة.
(Memorial)
(النصب التذكاري)
Minister of Rites, Zhou Kaiping,
وزير الطقوس ، زو كايبينغ ،
has already leaked out
قد تسربت بالفعل
the imperial examination questions.
أسئلة الامتحان الإمبراطوري.
However, who has bought it
ومع ذلك ، من قام بشرائها
and how much he has exposed,
وكم كشف ،
I need time to investigate.
أنا بحاجة إلى وقت للتحقيق.
They're jeopardising the country.
إنهم يعرضون البلد للخطر.
Keep the investigation going.
استمر في التحقيق.
Yes.
نعم.
(Shen Zhihuan)
(شين زيهوان)
(wants to save Shen family.)
(يريد أن ينقذ عائلة شين.)
(Maybe I can...)
(ربما أستطيع ...)
Yanqing,
يانكينغ ،
I've made this medicine for you.
لقد صنعت هذا الدواء من أجلك.
It's just right
إنه مجرد حق
to drink it now.
لتشربه الآن.
I'm not ill.
لست مريضا.
Why do I need to drink the medicine?
لماذا احتاج لشرب الدواء؟
Yanqing,
يانكينغ ،
although we're
على الرغم من أننا
not biological siblings,
ليسوا أشقاء بيولوجيين ،
it's been so many years,
لقد مرت سنوات عديدة ،
I've always looked at you as my only family member.
لطالما نظرت إليك كعضو عائلتي الوحيد.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
you don't have to
ليس عليك ذلك
hide certain thing from me.
إخفاء شيء معين عني.
Mengchun,
Mengchun ،
what are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Take your medicine and leave.
خذ دوائك وغادر.
Yanqing,
يانكينغ ،
don't hide your illness.
لا تخفي مرضك.
You should
يجب
think about your children and your grandchildren.
فكر في أطفالك وأحفادك.
It's just...
انه فقط...
It's just that your kidneys
إنها مجرد كليتيك
are bad.
سيئة.
The physician said that
قال الطبيب ذلك
as long as you take the medicine,
ما دمت تأخذ الدواء ،
you'll be well.
ستكون بخير.
Who told that?
من قال ذلك؟
I'm only giving you one chance.
أنا فقط أعطيك فرصة واحدة.
It's
إنه
Shen Zhihuan.
شين تشيهوان.
I can finally drink milk tea.
يمكنني أخيرًا شرب شاي الحليب.
Shen Zhihuan!
شين تشيهوان!
You pervert!
أنت المنحرف!
Xu Yanqing, what are you doing?
شو يانكينغ ، ماذا تفعل؟
I'm warning you.
أنا أحذرك.
Don't go crazy.
لا تصاب بالجنون.
Otherwise, I'll not go easy on you.
خلاف ذلك ، لن أيسر عليك.
Miss!
يفتقد!
What's wrong,
ما هو الخطأ،
Miss?
يفتقد؟
Xu Yanqing.
شو يانكينغ.
I...
أنا...
I know you don't like me
اعرف انك لا تحبني
and you don't want to touch me.
وأنت لا تريد أن تلمسني.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
If you obey me tonight
إذا أطعتني الليلة
and be my woman,
وكوني امرأتي ،
I'll protect you.
سأحميك.
How does it sound?
كيف يبدو صوته؟
After all, I'm holding a high position.
بعد كل شيء ، أنا في منصب رفيع.
No one can harm me.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يؤذيني.
(When you're thirty years old)
(عندما تبلغ الثلاثين من العمر)
(and being killed by the rebels,)
(ويقتلهم المتمردون)
(you won't talk like this.)
(لن تتحدث هكذا).
(Why does this stupid woman)
(لماذا هذه المرأة الغبية)
(keep saying that I'll be killed by the rebels at 30 years old?)
(استمر بالقول أنني سأقتل على يد المتمردين في سن الثلاثين؟)
(Who is she actually?)
(من هي في الواقع؟)
(Miss!)
(يفتقد!)
(Yanqing!)
(يانكينغ!)
Please be rational!
من فضلك كن عقلاني!
Miss!
يفتقد!
Yanqing!
يانكينغ!
(Open the door!)
(افتح الباب!)
(If I go out now,)
(إذا خرجت الآن ،)
(the rumour of my kidney failure will be proven true.)
(سوف تثبت صحة إشاعة الفشل الكلوي).
Put me down!
انزلني!
- Miss! - Yanqing!
- آنسة! - يانكينغ!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Put me down!
انزلني!